<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moeti Mphoso</title>
    <link>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Moeti Mphoso</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:11:56 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stanbic Talk - Modern Data Plartform [!published draft]</title>
      <link>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/posts/stanbic-talk-modern-data-plartform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:11:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/posts/stanbic-talk-modern-data-plartform/</guid>
      <description>Infrastructure as code, encoding configuration
link to terraform why:
elasticity automation reusability version control scalable Day 0 and Day 1 activities. Day 1: “Day 1” refers to OS and application configurations you apply after you’ve initially built your infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python application distribution [!published draft]</title>
      <link>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/posts/python-package-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 12:11:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/posts/python-package-distribution/</guid>
      <description>Desired results You want to easily distribute and share your application with your users (including other developers). You want your application to be installed via pip. pip install my-awesome-application You want to access your application in your other projects on your computer. import my-awesome-application You want to be able to run your application from the terminal as standalone, without having to execute it via python and specifying or navigating to your project folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 12:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>resume pdf
Who am I? My name is Moeti Mphoso and I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Engineer. I&amp;rsquo;m from Lesotho, living in South Africa and currently working at HISP-SA. Python &amp;amp; Golang programming enthusiast, Open source software contributer. Expertise in database modeling &amp;amp; implementation, &amp;amp; data integration. CAPM Certified.
What is this Site? My current interests &amp;amp; what im working on soft skills
argument construction &amp;amp; presentation decision making getting collaboration from team &amp;amp; having effective meetings organizing work &amp;amp; getting things done health optimization (memory &amp;amp; energy) stream processing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Zero [!published draft]</title>
      <link>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 16:34:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Moeti-Mphoso.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>the idea behind this blog.
Reflexions is my number one habit that helps me improve and solve problems, it works mostly on my value of continuous improvement. This is the habit i most want to improve above all others, my hope for this blog is that it will cement my resolve and commitment to this habit, i have a tendency to slag on it and not reflect as much as i want, hopefully the social pressure of doing this will push me in the direction i know i really really want, in essence, I’m putting myself in a corner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
